{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "If you _____ me, I would have come .",
      "correctAnswer": "had called",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have called"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _____ that book, I would have known the answer .",
      "correctAnswer": "had read",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have read"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we _____ him, we would have believed him .",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "haven't known"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we _____ earlier, we would have caught a train .",
      "correctAnswer": "had left",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have left"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he _____ better, he would have got a job .",
      "correctAnswer": "had studied",
      "incorrectAnswers": "has studied"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I hadn't called you, you _____ the news .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have known"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I had bought that watch yesterday, I _____ all my money .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have spent",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will have spend"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I hadn't been so rude to him, we _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have argued",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have argued"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I had told her the way, she _____ lost .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have got",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have got"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you had set up an alarm clock, you _____ late .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have been",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have been"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ a coat if I had been cold .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have worn",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had worn"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ your exam if you had worked harder .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have passed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had passed"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ a cake if I had known you were coming .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have baked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had baked"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ to you if you had given me your e-mail .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had written"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ you a present if I had known it was your birthday .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have bought",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had bought"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would have met him if I _____ he was in town last week .",
      "correctAnswer": "had known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have known"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would have come yesterday if I _____ time .",
      "correctAnswer": "had had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have had"
    },
    {
      "question": "We would have watched the movie if they _____ earlier .",
      "correctAnswer": "had come",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have come"
    },
    {
      "question": "They would have been happy if they _____ married .",
      "correctAnswer": "had got",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have got"
    },
    {
      "question": "You might have liked this dish if you _____ it .",
      "correctAnswer": "had tried",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have tried"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "If you _____ # me, I would have come .",
      "correctAnswer": "had called",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have called"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _____ # that book, I would have known the answer .",
      "correctAnswer": "had read",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have read"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we _____ # him, we would have believed him .",
      "correctAnswer": "hadn't known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "haven't known"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we _____ # earlier, we would have caught a train .",
      "correctAnswer": "had left",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have left"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he _____ # better, he would have got a job .",
      "correctAnswer": "had studied",
      "incorrectAnswers": "has studied"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I hadn't called you, you _____ # the news .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have known"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I had bought that watch yesterday, I _____ # all my money .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have spent",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will have spend"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I hadn't been so rude to him, we _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have argued",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have argued"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I had told her the way, she _____ # lost .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have got",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have got"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you had set up an alarm clock, you _____ # late .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't have been",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't have been"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # a coat if I had been cold .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have worn",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had worn"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ # your exam if you had worked harder .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have passed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had passed"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # a cake if I had known you were coming .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have baked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had baked"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # to you if you had given me your e-mail .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had written"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # you a present if I had known it was your birthday .",
      "correctAnswer": "would have bought",
      "incorrectAnswers": "would had bought"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would have met him if I _____ # he was in town last week .",
      "correctAnswer": "had known",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have known"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would have come yesterday if I _____ # time .",
      "correctAnswer": "had had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have had"
    },
    {
      "question": "We would have watched the movie if they _____ # earlier .",
      "correctAnswer": "had come",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have come"
    },
    {
      "question": "They would have been happy if they _____ # married .",
      "correctAnswer": "had got",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have got"
    },
    {
      "question": "You might have liked this dish if you _____ # it .",
      "correctAnswer": "had tried",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have tried"
    }
  ]
}